Austin Cuddeback

ajcuddeback@gmail.com | (863) 245-3982 | Lakeland, FL

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/austin-cuddeback-b3aba7197/

GitHub: https://github.com/ajcuddeback

Portfolio: https://ajcuddeback.github.io/react-portfolio

Summary

Driven Full-Stack Developer with two years of Web Development Experience. Strong problem-solving and development skills. Team player with an eye for detail. I am experienced with HTML, CSS, Node, APIs, Databases (SQL and MongoDB), React.js, AWS/Azure, and Ubuntu instances.

Work Experience

Amesite 05/2021 – Current Jr. Developer Remote

- Implemented regular bug fixes, features, and hotfixes in Amesite's SaaS platform utilizing Angular, Node, and Postgres database.
- Researched and architected improvements to the platform's Authentication flow leveraging Auth0, decreasing response times on the platform while increasing security.
- Created a proposal for the use of TDD utilizing JEST to the team, which gained great feedback
 and support, leading to us implementing it in the code stack, providing a more secure and
 efficient way of coding.
- Helped build, optimize, and architect dev and prod instances leveraging Azure's VM's, AWS
 S3, Cognito, Cloud Front and Lambda functions, Linux, and Ansible.
- Architected multiple new features, improvements, and cloud-based infrastructure.
- Conducted interviews with engineering candidates.

Hernando Reptile Rescue 11/2020 – 04/2021 Full Stack Developer/Web Maintenance Supervisor Lakeland, FL

- Migrated the Clients website from a wix.com website to a Full Stack website within a deadline of 2 weeks leveraging HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Express, and MySQL.
- Developed a RESTful API allowing owners to add their animals to the website through an administrator page.

Skills

Front-End

- React
- Angular
- Javascript
- TypeScript
- Cookies

- HTML5
- CSS (SASS, SCSS, bootstrap)
- Animations
- Adobe XD

Back-end

- Node.js
- Express.js
- APIs (RESTful and GraphQL)
- Bcrypt
- Sails.js
- Auth0

- MySQL
- SQL ORM's (Sequelize)
- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- Stripe.js

Dev-Ops

- Azure (VM's, Blob, CDN)
- Linux

- AWS (S3, Lambda, Cloud Front, Cognito)
- Ubuntu

Education

University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL From 2020-2021 Full-Stack Web Development Certificate